{
  "title": "Idioms with the phrasal verb pass",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The World Congress of Georgian Jews yesterday announced the ........ of their head rabbi.",
      "answers": [
        "passing through",
        "passing by",
        "passing away",
        "passing round"
      ],
      "correct": "passing away"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Entrepreneurs have several options when it comes to ........ a family business to their children.",
      "answers": ["passing over", "passing out", "passing by", "passing on"],
      "correct": "passing on"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Don't ........ your opportunity to increase sales by leveraging the power of email marketing.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass out", "pass by", "pass round"],
      "correct": "pass up"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Once you ........ Prospect Street, we will be on the right hand side of the block, directly across the street from the museum.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass out", "pass away", "pass over"],
      "correct": "pass over"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "If you were to ........ suddenly, your business could be tied up in probate court for several years.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass out", "pass away", "pass over"],
      "correct": "pass away"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Lawmakers shouldn't ........ the chance to regulate tobacco.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass out", "pass away", "pass over"],
      "correct": "pass up"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "I can make myself ......... I do it by taking in a deep breath and then pushing all that air down. It takes me about 15 seconds.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass out", "pass over", "pass by"],
      "correct": "pass out"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Foreign companies will have to ........ the hat to pay for the extra costs of doing business in Indonesia.",
      "answers": ["pass up", "pass by", "pass round", "pass over"],
      "correct": "pass round"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Approximately 27,000 â€” 29,000 vehicles ........ the Detroit-Windsor Tunnel on a daily basis.",
      "answers": ["pass through", "pass out", "pass away", "pass on"],
      "correct": "pass through"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The ........ game is just a preadolescent version of autoerotic asphyxia paraphilia.",
      "answers": ["pass through", "pass out", "pass by", "pass over"],
      "correct": "pass out"
    }
  ]
}
